<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<component type="desktop-application">
  <id>io.github.igonzalezb.qsl-generator</id>
  
  <name>QSL Card Generator</name>
  <summary>Bulk QSL card generator for radio amateurs</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="es">Generador masivo de tarjetas QSL para radioaficionados</summary>
  
  <metadata_license>FSFAP</metadata_license>
  <project_license>GPL-3.0</project_license> 
  
  <description>
    <p>A desktop application for amateur radio operators designed to generate QSL cards in bulk from ADIF log files. Built with Python, PyQt6, and Pillow.</p>
    <p xml:lang="es">Una aplicación de escritorio para radioaficionados diseñada para generar tarjetas QSL en masa a partir de archivos de registro ADIF. Construida con Python, PyQt6 y Pillow.</p>

    <p>Features:</p>
    <p xml:lang="es">Características:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>ADIF Import: Load contacts directly from your favorite logging software.</li>
      <li xml:lang="es">Importación ADIF: Carga contactos directamente desde tu software favorito.</li>

      <li>Live Preview: See your QSL card updates in real time.</li>
      <li xml:lang="es">Vista Previa en Vivo: Ve los cambios en tiempo real.</li>

      <li>Highly Customizable: Change table background and text colors, adjust transparency, and choose from 7 predefined table positions.</li>
      <li xml:lang="es">Altamente Personalizable: Cambia colores de fondo y texto, ajusta la transparencia, y elige entre 7 posiciones predefinidas.</li>

      <li>Manual Editing: Edit contact data directly in the table.</li>
      <li xml:lang="es">Edición Manual: Edita contactos directamente en la tabla.</li>

      <li>Fast Batch Export: Uses multithreaded background processing.</li>
      <li xml:lang="es">Exportación Rápida: Usa procesamiento multihilo.</li>

      <li>Multilingual: English and Spanish support with automatic detection.</li>
      <li xml:lang="es">Multilingüe: Soporte para inglés y español.</li>

      <li>Settings Persistence: Saves your preferences for future sessions.</li>
      <li xml:lang="es">Persistencia: Guarda preferencias automáticamente.</li>
    </ul>

    <p>This is a personal project developed for the amateur radio community. Feedback, suggestions, and contributions are always welcome! 73 and good DX!</p>
    <p xml:lang="es">Este es un proyecto personal desarrollado para la comunidad de radioaficionados. ¡Las sugerencias y contribuciones son bienvenidas! 73 y buen DX!</p>
  </description>
  
  <launchable type="desktop-id">qsl-generator.desktop</launchable>
  
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <image>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/igonzalezb/QSL-Card-Generator/refs/heads/main/docs/main_window_eng.png</image>
      <caption>Main window of the application</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="es">Ventana principal de la aplicación</caption>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>

  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <image>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/igonzalezb/QSL-Card-Generator/refs/heads/main/docs/main_window_eng.png</image>
      <caption>Main window of the application</caption>
    </screenshot>
    
    <screenshot>
      <image xml:lang="es">https://raw.githubusercontent.com/igonzalezb/QSL-Card-Generator/refs/heads/main/docs/main_window_spa.png</image>
      <caption xml:lang="es">Ventana principal de la aplicación</caption>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  
  <url type="homepage">https://igonzalezb.github.io/QSL-Card-Generator/</url>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://github.com/igonzalezb/QSL-Card-Generator/issues</url>
  
  <developer_name>LU2EXV</developer_name>
  
  <releases>
    <release version="0.3.1" date="2026-04-29">
      <description>
        <p>Initial AppImage release.</p>
        <p xml:lang="es">Lanzamiento inicial.</p>
      </description>
    </release>
  </releases>
</component>